Stephen Rivas Jr.

Project Manager Web & Mobile Developer



Hello, my name is Stephen Rivas Jr., I am a web developer and project manager. In my experience developers, clients, and project managers all speak different languages while building toward the same end goal. I speak all three languages. I aim to keep communication effective, and make sure every member of the project team - clients included - are all able to understand and produce optimal solutions.

Awards & Honors

Valedictorian

Class of 2011 - Full Sail University

Advanced Achievement

Class of 2011 - Full Sail University

Audience Choice Award

NodeJam Entry, NodeSummit 2011

WorldVision Design Contest

Rebrand/Energize Proposal

Course Director Awards

2009 - 2011 Full Sail University Mobile Device Development Deployment of Flash Projects Web Project Preproduction Flex Frameworks Applied Design Tools & Interfaces

Focus & Skills

languages: [node.js, coffeescript, javascript, php, coldfusion, stylus, jade];

databases: [neo4i, couchdb, redis, mysal, monao];

concepts: [mvc, mvvm, rvp, module pattern, oop, prototype, user experience design];

productivity: [AtTask, TeamBox, Git, BaseCamp, Wunderlist];

Career

Zeunic, LLC . Orlando, July 2011 - Current

owner; project manager, developer

- Day-to-Day Business Management
- Generated \$500k+ Online Client Revenue
- Project & Client Account Management Achieved Over 1 million combined page views
- Server Side Development

Freelance Developer. Orlando, Nov 2009 - July 2011

self-employed; web developer, front-end designer

- Consulted with clients to define project vision and goals
- Produced Solutions for multiple small businesses
- Balanced multiple projects, school, and life

inBurst Design Solutions. Northern Colorado, 2003 - 2006

owner; web developer, front-end designer

- Collaborated with Industry Leaders
- Produced Solutions for multiple small and
- Active Chamber of Commerce Member medium sized businesses

Education

Full Sail University . 2009 - 2011

Bachelor of Science Degree Major in Web Design & Development Online Courses / Self Taught . 1999 - current

Familiar with multiple venues of online on-going learning

Stephen Rivas Jr Longwood, Florida phone. 407.615.0794 email. me@stephenrivasjr.com www.stephenrivasjr.com